Morgan Petersen

616-232-7644 · morgan.petersen2020@gmail.com · Portfolio Link 812 E Kingsley St, Ann Arbor, MI 48104

Software Engineering, Data Analysis and Game Development

I am a University of Michigan 2024 graduate with a degree in Computer Science and a minor in Statistics. I have a strong programming background, with a specific passion for creating appealing visual experiences, from video games, to data visualizations, to frontend programming. I also really enjoy learning new skills on the fly, so I'd love to learn new technical skills in any area!

Key Competencies

Prog. Languages: C++, JavaScript, C#, R Project experience in HTML/CSS

Project experience using Bootstrap & Vue.js Some experience with Python, Java Project experience prototyping with Figma Some experience with SQL Queries

Proficiency using C# with Unity Engine Work experience with Git and Jira Work exp. in React Native, JavaScript Experience writing documentation

Project experience using REST API Project experience with SPSS Statistics

Professional Experience

WolverineSoft Studio **Game Programmer, QA Director**

May 2023 - May 2024

Used Unity and C# to develop fun computer games, including two single-player games and an online multiplayer title, all of which can be found on my portfolio and Steam. As QA Director, I was responsible for finding and reporting bugs, fixing as many as possible, and organizing and leading the rest of the QA team. My programming and leadership skills ensured all these titles released in as polished a state as possible.

Ford Motor Co Software Development Intern

May 2023 - Aug 2023

Worked on the SYNC 4 development team, where I wrote and debugged JavaScript code, iterating upon existing React Native components for Ford SYNC 4 systems. Specifically, I implemented a Storybook app for React Native which helped with component testing. I also created a functional temperature dial graphic using Skia which conformed to graphic prototypes created in Figma. My efforts in feature development and bugfixing helped create seamless functionality before each periodic release date.

Nuvu Fuels April 2018 - Aug 2022

Inventory Associate

Organized and restocked beverage displays to optimize the convenience store's visual appeal. In addition, I received deliveries from distribution companies and organized the cooler area following deliveries, ensuring an efficient stocking experience for all teammates.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Bachelor of Science and Engineering

Major: Computer Science

Minor: Statistics

University of Michigan - Ann Arbor

3.3 GPA

PEERRS Human Subjects Protection Certification

University of Michigan

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Competitive Director, Esports Club - Rocket League University of Michigan

Member, WolverineSoft Games Club

University of Michigan